[{"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Noor is working as a barista at a busy coffee shop. Noor wants to make a delicious cappuccino for a customer. Noor grabs a milk pitcher and fills it with almond milk.\nQuestion: Does Noor believe the milk pitcher contains oat milk or almond milk?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Noor believes the milk pitcher contains almond milk.\nb)Noor believes the milk pitcher contains oat milk.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Noor is working as a barista at a busy coffee shop. Noor wants to make a delicious cappuccino for a customer. Noor grabs a milk pitcher and fills it with oat milk.\nQuestion: Does Noor believe the milk pitcher contains oat milk or almond milk?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Noor believes the milk pitcher contains almond milk.\nb)Noor believes the milk pitcher contains oat milk.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [2360, 269], "obj_len": 2}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Zara is attending an art exhibition at a local gallery in her town. Zara wants to learn more about a particular abstract painting she admires. The label next to the artwork states that the painting is the work of a emerging artist, and Zara reads the label carefully.\nQuestion: Does Zara believe the painting is the work of a emerging artist or an emerging artist?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Zara believes the painting is the work of an emerging artist.\nb)Zara believes the painting is the work of a emerging artist.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Zara is attending an art exhibition at a local gallery in her town. Zara wants to learn more about a particular abstract painting she admires. The label next to the artwork states that the painting is the work of a famous artist, and Zara reads the label carefully.\nQuestion: Does Zara believe the painting is the work of a famous artist or an emerging artist?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Zara believes the painting is the work of an emerging artist.\nb)Zara believes the painting is the work of a famous artist.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [1901, 5169], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Carlos is a farmer in a small village in Mexico, tending to his cornfield. Carlos wants to irrigate his crops by using a water valve connected to a nearby river. Carlos opened the valve the previous evening.\nQuestion: Does Carlos believe the water valve is closed or open?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Carlos believes the water valve is closed.\nb)Carlos believes the water valve is open.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Carlos is a farmer in a small village in Mexico, tending to his cornfield. Carlos wants to irrigate his crops by using a water valve connected to a nearby river. Carlos closed the valve the previous evening.\nQuestion: Does Carlos believe the water valve is closed or open?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Carlos believes the water valve is closed.\nb)Carlos believes the water valve is open.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [53391], "corrupt_agent_name": [30397], "obj_len": 1}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kofi is a fisherman from a small village in Ghana. Kofi wants to catch enough fish today to provide for his family and sell the surplus at the market. Kofi torn his fishing net last night.\nQuestion: Does Kofi believe his fishing net is in good condition or torn apart?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kofi believes his fishing net is in good condition.\nb)Kofi believes his fishing net is torn apart.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kofi is a fisherman from a small village in Ghana. Kofi wants to catch enough fish today to provide for his family and sell the surplus at the market. Kofi repaired his fishing net last night.\nQuestion: Does Kofi believe his fishing net is in good condition or torn apart?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kofi believes his fishing net is in good condition.\nb)Kofi believes his fishing net is torn apart.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [735, 93123], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Azola is a teacher at a small school in rural China. Azola wants to surprise her students. Azola got a notification from Amazon stating that the package containing the hand-knit scarf was left at her doorstep.\nQuestion: Does Azola believe the package contains the book she ordered or a hand-knit scarf?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Azola believes the package contains the book she ordered.\nb)Azola believes the package contains a hand-knit scarf.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Azola is a teacher at a small school in rural China. Azola wants to surprise her students. Azola got a notification from Amazon stating that the package containing the book was left at her doorstep.\nQuestion: Does Azola believe the package contains the book she ordered or a hand-knit scarf?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Azola believes the package contains the book she ordered.\nb)Azola believes the package contains a hand-knit scarf.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [15757, 8083], "obj_len": 4}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kofi is a chef at a popular Ghanaian restaurant. Kofi wants to prepare a traditional groundnut soup for the dinner menu. Kofi adds a small container of tomato sauce to the soup pot on the stove.\nQuestion: Does Kofi believe the soup contains peanut butter or tomato paste?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kofi believes the soup contains tomato paste.\nb)Kofi believes the soup contains peanut butter.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kofi is a chef at a popular Ghanaian restaurant. Kofi wants to prepare a traditional groundnut soup for the dinner menu. Kofi adds a small container of peanut butter to the soup pot on the stove.\nQuestion: Does Kofi believe the soup contains peanut butter or tomato paste?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kofi believes the soup contains tomato paste.\nb)Kofi believes the soup contains peanut butter.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [735, 93123], "obj_len": 2}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kael is a farmer in a remote village in the Andes. Kael wants to plant a new crop of high-altitude potatoes in one of his terraced fields. The soil in the field appears mostly rocky dirt.\nQuestion: Does Kael believe the soil is rich and well-fertilized or mostly rocky dirt?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kael believes the soil is rich and well-fertilized.\nb)Kael believes the soil is mostly rocky dirt.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Kael is a farmer in a remote village in the Andes. Kael wants to plant a new crop of high-altitude potatoes in one of his terraced fields. The soil in the field appears rich and well-fertilized.\nQuestion: Does Kael believe the soil is rich and well-fertilized or mostly rocky dirt?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Kael believes the soil is rich and well-fertilized.\nb)Kael believes the soil is mostly rocky dirt.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [735, 6015], "obj_len": 5}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Farhan is a street food vendor in a bustling market in Istanbul. Farhan wants to prepare a delicious chicken shawarma wrap for a customer. Farhan takes a bottle of hot sauce from the shelf and pours it onto the shawarma wrap.\nQuestion: Does Farhan believe the sauce he poured is garlic sauce or hot sauce?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Farhan believes the sauce he poured is hot sauce.\nb)Farhan believes the sauce he poured is garlic sauce.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Farhan is a street food vendor in a bustling market in Istanbul. Farhan wants to prepare a delicious chicken shawarma wrap for a customer. Farhan takes a bottle of garlic sauce from the shelf and pours it onto the shawarma wrap.\nQuestion: Does Farhan believe the sauce he poured is garlic sauce or hot sauce?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Farhan believes the sauce he poured is hot sauce.\nb)Farhan believes the sauce he poured is garlic sauce.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [13759, 10118], "obj_len": 2}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Abhay is a young farmer in a small Indian village. Abhay wants to water his crops with the water stored in a large clay pot. Abhay checks the water level and sees that the pot is empty.\nQuestion: Does Abhay believe the pot is full of water or empty?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Abhay believes the pot is empty.\nb)Abhay believes the pot is full of water.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Abhay is a young farmer in a small Indian village. Abhay wants to water his crops with the water stored in a large clay pot. Abhay checks the water level and sees that the pot is full.\nQuestion: Does Abhay believe the pot is full of water or empty?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Abhay believes the pot is empty.\nb)Abhay believes the pot is full of water.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [3765, 68412], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Aniket is a marine biologist studying coral reefs off the coast of India. Aniket needs to collect samples of coral to analyze the effects of climate change on the reef. Aniket spots a damaged coral formation in a specific area of the reef.\nQuestion: Does Aniket believe the coral formation is healthy or damaged?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Aniket believes the coral formation is healthy.\nb)Aniket believes the coral formation is damaged.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Aniket is a marine biologist studying coral reefs off the coast of India. Aniket needs to collect samples of coral to analyze the effects of climate change on the reef. Aniket spots a healthy-looking coral formation in a specific area of the reef.\nQuestion: Does Aniket believe the coral formation is healthy or damaged?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Aniket believes the coral formation is healthy.\nb)Aniket believes the coral formation is damaged.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [735, 2303, 7304], "corrupt_agent_name": [1556, 1609, 295], "obj_len": 1}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Lila is a beekeeper in a small village in Eastern Europe. Lila wants to harvest honey from one of her beehives. The beehive is nearly empty, as Lila observed during her last inspection.\nQuestion: Does Lila believe the beehive is full of honey or nearly empty?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Lila believes the beehive is full of honey.\nb)Lila believes the beehive is nearly empty.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Lila is a beekeeper in a small village in Eastern Europe. Lila wants to harvest honey from one of her beehives. The beehive is full of honey, as Lila observed during her last inspection.\nQuestion: Does Lila believe the beehive is full of honey or nearly empty?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Lila believes the beehive is full of honey.\nb)Lila believes the beehive is nearly empty.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [445, 10746], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Hiroshi is a fisherman in a small coastal village in Japan. Hiroshi wants to catch some fish to provide dinner for his family. Hiroshi checks the weather forecast and sees that it will be rainstrom throughout the day.\nQuestion: Does Hiroshi believe the weather will be sunny or does he expect a rainstorm?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Hiroshi believes there will be a rainstorm.\nb)Hiroshi believes the weather will be sunny all day.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Hiroshi is a fisherman in a small coastal village in Japan. Hiroshi wants to catch some fish to provide dinner for his family. Hiroshi checks the weather forecast and sees that it will be sunny throughout the day.\nQuestion: Does Hiroshi believe the weather will be sunny or does he expect a rainstorm?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Hiroshi believes there will be a rainstorm.\nb)Hiroshi believes the weather will be sunny all day.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [57392, 60521], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Juan is a young chef in a small Mexican town. Juan wants to make a delicious salsa for the upcoming town festival. Juan buys fresh tomatoes from the market, which he believes are crushed and unsuitable for the salsa.\nQuestion: Does Juan believe the tomatoes are ripe and perfect or crushed and unsuitable?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Juan believes the tomatoes are ripe and perfect.\nb)Juan believes the tomatoes are crushed and unsuitable.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Juan is a young chef in a small Mexican town. Juan wants to make a delicious salsa for the upcoming town festival. Juan buys fresh tomatoes from the market, which he believes are ripe and perfect for the salsa.\nQuestion: Does Juan believe the tomatoes are ripe and perfect or crushed and unsuitable?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Juan believes the tomatoes are ripe and perfect.\nb)Juan believes the tomatoes are crushed and unsuitable.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [53391], "corrupt_agent_name": [29604], "obj_len": 3}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Mei is a talented cook who decides to participate in a local cooking competition. Mei wants to prepare a delicious dish using a fresh basket of vegetables from her garden. Mei sees that the vegetables are wilted and less fresh.\nQuestion: Does Mei believe the vegetables are fresh and vibrant or wilted and less fresh?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Mei believes the vegetables are wilted and less fresh.\nb)Mei believes the vegetables are fresh and vibrant.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " a", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Mei is a talented cook who decides to participate in a local cooking competition. Mei wants to prepare a delicious dish using a fresh basket of vegetables from her garden. Mei sees that the vegetables are freshly picked and vibrant.\nQuestion: Does Mei believe the vegetables are fresh and vibrant or wilted and less fresh?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Mei believes the vegetables are wilted and less fresh.\nb)Mei believes the vegetables are fresh and vibrant.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " b", "clean_agent_name": [53391], "corrupt_agent_name": [92033], "obj_len": 4}, {"clean_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Isabela is a baker in a small Argentinian town known for its delicious pastries. Isabela wants to make a batch of alfajores, a traditional Argentinian dessert, for her bakery's customers. Isabela gets a bag of flour from her pantry to dust the alfajores.\nQuestion: Does Isabela believe the bag she took from the pantry contains powdered sugar or flour?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Isabela believes the bag she took from the pantry contains powdered sugar.\nb)Isabela believes the bag she took from the pantry contains flour.\nAnswer:", "clean_target": " b", "corrupt_prompt": "Instructions: Keep track of people's knowledge defined in the story. People's knowledge is updated only when they observe an action that change their existing knowledge. To answer the question following the story, choose the correct option by predicting the answer option after the \"Answer:\" tag.\n\nStory: Isabela is a baker in a small Argentinian town known for its delicious pastries. Isabela wants to make a batch of alfajores, a traditional Argentinian dessert, for her bakery's customers. Isabela gets a bag of powdered sugar from her pantry to dust the alfajores.\nQuestion: Does Isabela believe the bag she took from the pantry contains powdered sugar or flour?\nChoose one of the following:\na)Isabela believes the bag she took from the pantry contains powdered sugar.\nb)Isabela believes the bag she took from the pantry contains flour.\nAnswer:", "corrupt_target": " a", "clean_agent_name": [22300, 76423], "corrupt_agent_name": [2209, 38485], "obj_len": 2}]